Hey, what's wrong?
どうしたの、ちょっと
I'm tired.
疲れちゃった
Are you tired?
疲れたの?
You're laughing so hard.
めっちゃ笑ってるじゃん
We had a lot of sex.
た くさんエッチしちゃったね
Are you really tired?
さすがに疲れたの?
It felt good.
気持ちよくて
I felt so good that I was tired.
気持ちよかったから疲れちゃった
What felt good?
何が気持ちよかったの?
Where?
どこが?
specifically.
具体的に
all.
全部
Oh, really?
あ、そう?
Good, good.
よかったよかった
We were a good match, see you then.
相性がよかったんだね、じゃあね
penis.
おちんちん
I'm falling asleep.
爆睡です
Get some rest.
ちょっとゆっくり休んで
Take a break and take a moment.
ゆっくり休んで、ちょっと
I'd better get out of here soon.
早くここから出たほうがいいよ
Because you'll be attacked again.
また襲われちゃうから
I'll come again.
また 来ちゃうから
Looks like a friend.
友っぽい
Did you come?
来てくれたの?
I'm here.
来ちゃいました
Have you come?
来ちゃいました?
I said "I'm here" one more time.
来ちゃいましたって言ってもう一回
I'm here.
来ちゃいました
What did you come for?
何しに来たの?
picture?
え?
For what?
何しに?
Yeah.
うん
Did you come for eight?
エイトしに来ました?
Okay, just a little.
いいですよ、ちょっと
Can I ask you to say it again?
もう一回言ってもらっていいですか?
I came for eight.
エイトしに来ました
That's no good, right?
ダメでしょ
How old are you now?
今何歳だっけ?
I'm 18 now.
今18です
It's OK.
OKなんか
Is it OK?
OKか
I think it was around the time we first met.
初めて会った時のぐらいだった気がするけど
Well, let's leave that aside for a moment.
まぁそれはちょっと置いときましょう
Well, I'm going back to school now.
え、 今学校帰ってる
It seems like the units are a little weird.
なんかちょっと 単位がやばいみたいな
Looks like I'll turn it into a limine.
リミネにしちゃうみたいな
That's what I said.
言 ってたけど
It's a little scary.
ちょっとやばい
Seriously.
まじで
terrible?
やばい?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
An exam?
試験とか?
Promote to children.
子供へ推進
If you fall, it's over.
落ちたら終わり
picture?
え?
Oh, is it already over?
あ、もう終わった?
I should still be able to go.
まだいけるはず
Oh, are you still there?
あ、まだあんの?
test.
試験
I'm sure.
確かって
As you say, it's already over.
言ってる時点でもう終わってるわけですね
You haven't studied.
勉強してないじゃん
I'll do it after this.
この後します
Will it be over after this?
この後済むの?
I'll do it after this.
この後します
It would be dangerous if I didn't.
しないとやばいよね
Another year?
もう一年?
That's right.
そうだよね
But what have you done here?
でもここに何してきたの?
Here?
ここに?
I went to have sex.
えっちしに行きました
I want to give a credit.
単位あげたい
If I were a teacher, I would definitely give them credit.
俺が先生なら単位絶対あげたいけどね
I like honest people.
正直者は好きですよ
It's stressful.
ストレス溜まっちゃうもんね
on second thoughts.
やっぱり
Well then, if it goes well.
じゃあいければね
Especially now.
特に今
It's fun for a year or two though.
一、二年は楽しいけど
Yes, because it's not fun.
そう、楽しくないから
What is your career path?
進路は?
I'm not sure, but what is your specialty?
迷い中だけど、 専門?
I want to go to major.
専門行きたいなとか
What type are you?
何系ですか?
Like a nursery teacher.
保育士とか
That's fine.
いいじゃん
A naughty nursery teacher.
すけっぺな保育士
There are times when I say that I like my older brother.
年上のお兄さんが好きって 言ってる時がする
I can't be satisfied with just being my classmates.
同級生とかじゃ 満足できないもんね
yes.
はい
Oh, you had a boyfriend, didn't you?
あれ、彼氏いたんじゃない?
My boyfriend broke up with me recently.
彼氏はこの前別れました
picture?
え?
why?
なんで?
I'm busy studying.
勉強忙しくて
Did you shake it?
振ったの?
I was dumped.
振られた
I see, we were classmates, right?
そうか、同級生だったっけ?
I'll be studying for the entrance exam a little more over there.
向こうもうちょっと受験勉強とか
Wait, that's why you got dumped?
え、それで振られちゃったの?
I was rejected because I didn't study.
勉強しないから振られた
It's terrible, really.
ひどいね、本当に
That's right.
そうなんだ
By the way, I'm currently being promoted.
ちょっとじゃあ今昇進中だね
sad?
悲しい?
That's sad.
悲しいですね
I don't study at school, but I do study naughty.
学校の勉強はしないけど、 エッチな勉強するもんね、
full.
いっぱい
Fair enough.
まあまあ
He was really good.
めっちゃ優秀だったよね
Sensei today, I called you in today.
ちょっと今日先生、 先生をちょっと今日 お呼びしましたね
I'm sure you'll be satisfied.
きっと満足していただけると思う
Oh, hello.
あ、どうも
I'll give you a unit.
単位あげるよ
Yay!
やった!
I'll give you a unit.
単位あげるよ
So, is that it?
で、あれですか
You came here today because you wanted to hold a man.
今日はあなたがここに来たのは、 男を抱きたいと
I am the one who is held.
私抱かれる方です
I guess that's the age.
そういう年頃でしょう、だって
I'm interested in sex.
エッチに興味がある
There's no point in wearing a normal outfit, so
普通の格好しててもしょうがないので、
Let's talk while dressing a little modestly.
ちょっとはしたない格好しながら トークしましょう
Nice, the type you don't wear.
いいね、履いてないタイプね
It's a type of skirt without a guard.
ガードのないタイプのスカートね
That one is better.
そ っちの方優秀だね
You're getting excellent results.
優秀な成績を収めてるね
I guess you don't have sex with anyone other than your boyfriend?
エッチはじゃあ彼氏以外だと してない感じ?
Yeah, I haven't.
うん、してないです
So now I'm here without doing it.
じゃあ今、してない状態で来てる
If you give a score for horniness, out of 100,
ムラムラを点数で入れると、 100点満点中、
When you increase your horniness with points.
ムラムラを点数で上がると
That's excellent.
優秀だね
The average score is well above the passing score.
平均点をちゃんと 合格点を超えてるじゃん
I feel like I'm missing 5 more points, but I'll make up for it here.
あと5点は足りないのは、 ここで補う感じ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Now open your legs for yourself.
今こっちの足開いたね、自分で
While showing it?
見せながらに?
No.
違う よ
There's a nice wall here, so let's stand on it.
ここ にいい壁があるから、 そこに立ってみようか
nice
素敵な
Your skin is white.
肌、白いね
You have breasts, quite a lot.
おっぱいあるね、結構
Do you feel like you're sleeping?
寝てる感じ?
not at all.
全然
It's just that I don't get enough attention.
思われ足りないってことね
I'd like you to turn around and stick your butt out like this.
後ろ向いて、 こんな感じで、 お尻出してみてほしいんだけど
You have a nice butt.
いいお尻してるね
Isn't it jiggling?
プルプルじゃない?
this.
これ
I've been doing this all the time.
ずっとこれやってる
good?
いい?
I've been doing this for a long time.
ずっとこれやってて
I don't like it a bit.
ちょっと嫌だね
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
You know you're jiggling yourself, right?
自分でプルプルしてるの分かるでしょ?
My butt.
お尻が
That's a nice butt.
いいお尻だね
Can I take a deep breath?
深呼吸していい?
Dressed like this, I'm not thinking about doing my homework when I get home.
こんな格好しててさ、 お家帰ったら宿題やろうとか 考えてない
Right.
よね
Don't do that.
や めてよ、そういうの
I have to do it.
やんないと
Hey, let's get into a naughty mood now.
ちょっと、 今、エッチな気分になろうよ
It's the first time I've ever been here.
ここくりとり最初だって
That's easy to understand.
分かりやすいね
Let's take this off for now.
一旦脱いちゃおうか、これ
Your skin is so beautiful.
めっちゃお肌きれい
By the way, do you rant?
ちなみにさ、 おなりはするの?
sometimes?
たまに?
nice.
いいね
How does it feel?
どういう感じでするの?
What does it feel like?
どういう感じ?
refer to?
指?
Is that a kuritori scraping blade?
それはさ、くりとり擦り刃なの?
Or is there a command blade inside?
それとも中に指図刃なの?
Or is it something tricky?
それともなんかトリッキーなやつなの?
Only outside.
外だけだよ
Okay, just outside.
いいね、外だけだよって
So cute.
かわいいな
If you're in your pants, try it.
ちょっとパンツ上でいたら やってみて
You're definitely studying right now, right?
絶対勉強が今にやってるでしょ?
If you can't concentrate on studying, you're the type of person who becomes obedient, right?
勉強に集中できなくなったら おなりのタイプでしょ?
That's definitely the case now.
今のおなり絶対そうだよ
I'm used to it.
やり慣れてるもん
Oh no, I don't understand math.
やべえ、数学分かんねえ
That's right, it's like being quiet.
そうだ、おなりしろみたいな
different?
違う?
Really?
本当に?
It turned out to be an inner thigh, which is amazing.
内股になっちゃって、すごい
It was like this.
こういう感じだったよね
different,
違う、
different.
違う
Isn't it okay to turn around?
向 き振りいいじゃない?
Skirts will fall off even if you stand them, right?
スカート、スタンってしても落ちるでしょ?
Will it fall?
落ちるかな?
On the wall, like this.
壁にさ、こうやって
The moment you fall.
落ちる瞬間を
drop down?
落ちる?
It's okay.
いいじゃない
Please help me with the wall.
壁、ちょっと手つぎに手伝って
Do your legs a little and cross them.
足ちょっとやって、クロスして
This is like our gravure idol.
これ、僕らのグラビアアイドルみたい
It's a little wet.
ちょっと濡れてる
It's wet.
濡れてる
It's a little slimy.
ちょっとヌルっとしてる
You man?
ユーマン?
I'm going to take the test here.
ここテストに出るよ
No?
ダメ?
I'm sure this will be a test.
ここ、きっとテストに出ると思うよ
I'd like to make a bed.
ベッドをうっかけたいんだけど
No?
ダメ?
Is that no good?
それダメ?
It's no good if you don't have proper sex.
ちゃんとセックスがないとダメ
A little shallow, shallow.
ちょっと浅く、浅く
Chewy and shallow.
もち浅く
That's a really naughty pussy.
めちゃめちゃやらしいおまんこだね
Didn't you praise her pussy from the beginning?
元からおまんこ褒めたりしなかった?
I haven't.
してない
Don't you praise my pussy?
おまんこ褒めない?
I can feel it even in my butt.
ちょっとお尻の方まで感じる
It's starting to droop a little though.
ちょっと垂れてきてるけど
It would be great if there was a moisturized person like you in this dry world.
この乾いた世の中にあなたみたいな 潤いのある人がいたら 最高
That's right.
です よね
I really like Chestnut Toris.
栗トリス相当好きだね
As expected of a woman, there's nothing more than playing around with chestnuts.
さすが女に栗トリスいじるだけあるね
I bet you don't have one at home, right?
まさかおうちにあるところはないよね?
do not have.
ない
That's true.
本当ね
Let's take pictures of the good parts.
いいところは撮って撮ろう
Here.
ここって
How much do you like Chestnut Tris?
栗トリスこれくらいは好き?
Is this good?
これ いい?
Even the chestnuts here.
栗こっちにまで
You lived a cute life.
かわいい生き方したね
amazing.
すごい
a little bit.
ちょっと
I like this way of painting.
この塗り方いいね
I definitely want to lick this pussy.
このおまんこは絶対舐めたい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I even sent her to sleep school like this.
こんな寝学校にも出しちゃって
This won't appear on the test.
これはテストには出ないけど
Ah, here it is.
あ、これほら
Because it's slimy.
ぬるぬるだからね
Place only this foot on top of it and open it.
こっちの足だけその上にのけて開く
Lots of drool on the back.
裏のヨダリいっぱい
Come to think of it, what did you come here for?
そういえばここに何しに来たんだっけ?
What did you come here for?
ここに何しに来たんだっけ?
Can I have you try it again?
もう一回やってもらっていい?
I came for pliers.
ペンチしに来た
nice.
いいね
Place your hands on the wall and turn your butt towards me.
壁に手ついてお尻こっち向けて
It's really nice.
めっちゃいいね
It feels so good.
チンチン気持ちいいね
I said it.
言っちゃったね
I told you it felt so good.
チンチン気持ちいいって言っちゃったね
Isn't your pussy shaped like a penis?
おまんこチンチンの形になっちゃってるんじゃない?
Just this.
ちょっとこれ
Show me once.
一回見せて
It opened in the shape of a chin-chin.
チンチンの形に開いてた
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Shall we wait a little longer?
もうちょっと待ってみようか
Pull it once.
一回引いて
What did you come here for?
ここに何しに来たんだっけ?
I came for pliers.
ペンチしに来た
Did you come for pliers?
ペンチしに来た?
pliers
ペ ンチ
I came to see you.
し に来た
It's very tight.
すごい締め付ける
I can get rid of that tightness already.
そんな締め付けもうチンチン取れるさ
scared.
怖い
Your pussy is so wide open.
すごいパックリ開いてるよ、おまんこ
Are you going to go home and study?
帰って勉強するの?
I was jerking off there, but I just couldn't hold back.
そこでシコシコしてたんだけど、やっぱ我慢できない
I was surprised.
びっくりしたわ
No?
ダメ?
I was jerking off there.
そこでシコシコしてた
Splash some water.
水なんか弾いちゃって
One more time?
もう一回?
Do you hate hard people?
硬い人嫌い?
I don't hate it.
嫌いじゃないよ
I said it.
言っちゃった
current
今の
Don't you have a toy neck too?
あ なたも首トイスビンビンじゃない?
Get your hands on it.
手ついて
hear?
聞こえる?
This sound.
この音
What happened?
どうしちゃったの?
this.
これ
Are you excited?
興奮しちゃってる?
Maybe.
もしかして
Higa's legs.
ひがの足足
The hitesuri is also really cute though.
ひてすりもすごい可愛いんだけど
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
I can't make excuses anymore.
もう言い訳できない
Can I say it again?
もう一回言っていい?
You’re counting on me to feel good, right?
気持ちいいとか当てにきてるでしょ?
Finally, make it one.
最後、ひとつにして
I made a face like, “Huh?”
えーって顔した
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
I made it a little bigger.
ちょっと大きくしちゃった
You looked like, “Ah!”
あちゃーんって顔したね
nice.
いい ね
If I told you I could do this again in about 30 minutes, would you do it?
これ30分後くらいにまたできるって言ったらしてくれる?
You were fine.
元気だったね
How have you been?
元気だった?
thank you.
ありがとう